binaryoptions.net 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | BinaryOptions.net

**Privacy Policy**

BinaryOptions.net respects our users’ right to privacy.  We fully adhere to the UK Data Protection Act and we don’t collect any personal data from you unless it is strictly necessary (e.g. for competition prizes or broker complaints).

By using our website and reading out articles, you abide to the privacy policy here on this page.

**Users Privacy**

We do not collecting personal information from any of our users, except in cases where this is strictly necessary.  We do not pass on or sell your personal information to any third parties or operators.  If you would like to contact us or provide a complaint, can do so through our [contact page](http://www.binaryoptions.net/about-us/privacy-policy) here.

**Cookie Tracking Software**

Our website uses a number of different types of cookies which are necessary for the functioning and monetizing of our website.

Many of our links to third party websites use affiliate tracking links. This means that when you click on some of our links to binary options brokers, a harmless cookie will be installed on your computer for a period of 30-60 days.  These tracking cookies are necessary for the financial compensation of our website and tracking users to different websites.  The cookies themselves are not served by our website and we do not collect any personal information from them.

In addition to third party tracking cookies, our website also uses Analytics cookies to analyze website behavior and traffic on our site.  This is strictly necessary for monitoring our traffic (which we need proof of in order to negotiate media deals and sell banners), finding our most popular articles and seeing where our traffic is coming form.

**Affiliate Earnings Disclaimer**

BinaryOptions.net receives a good portion of its website revenue through affiliate marketing deals with binary options brokers.  Our website’s users are tracked to third party websites through tracking cookies.  This allows us to be financially compensated for sending traffic through to other websites.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Please note that we respect the right to make changes or updates to our privacy policy at any time without notifying you.  It is your responsible to check our privacy policy for future changes.

Rating: 0.0/ **5** (0 votes cast)
